dressve.com 2015-03-16

# 1.Privacy Policy – Dressve.com

On dressve.com, we take the protection for your Personal Information (such as name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; gender; language preference; and merchandise category preferences) very seriously.

We collect Personal Information that you provide to us voluntarily and process it for the following purposes ("Purposes"):

•to complete transactions with you and manage your membership of our customer loyalty scheme where applicable;

•to guide you the latest market trend;

•to understand and analyse our sales, and your needs and preferences;

•to develop, enhance, market and provide products and services to meet your needs;

•to enable you to participate in promotions and contests;

•to enable you to participate in customer research or focus groups;

•to process exchanges or product returns;

•to improve our competitiveness and service,

•to respond to requests or complaints.

dressve will respect your privacy and will pay attention to your online safety. We will record a variety of information from your visit to our site in order to provide the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates for you. You will see the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. All of this information which we made is in order to protect your privacy better.

OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS

Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests at the customer information section, or by telephoning, or emailing your request to www.dressve.com’s Customer Support department at service@dressve.com. Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information.

At first, thank you for accessing the website ("Site") of dressve.com. ("dressve.com," that's us). Your privacy will be respected and your personal information will be protected. If you want to know more information, you can read our privacy notice.

Though this privacy notice, you can know that how we collect, use, (and under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. Finally, you will know your options regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information with the privacy notice. You accept the practices described in this Notice by visiting our site.

You can apply this Privacy Notice only in this Site. So for our offline collection of your personal information, this privacy policy is not necessary. You will see the detail below. The content or privacy practices on any non-dressve.com website to which this Site links or that links to this Site is not our responsibility.
